<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Predefender Cyber Hunting</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/index.html</link>
    <description>Traditional Security Operations Centers (SOCs) are often reactive, constrained by a limited mindset that focuses on responding to threats as they emerge. But there’s a better approach. We’re here to transform SOC analysts into proactive threat hunters. Our cutting-edge training programs empower you to anticipate and neutralize threats before they strike, moving beyond mere reaction to true cybersecurity mastery. Embrace the proactive mindset and elevate your cybersecurity skills with us.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 10:37:22 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 10:37:22 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/index.html</guid>
      <description>Title Summary Published Date The Malware That Wasnt This article explores my journey of reverse engineering a mysterious malware sample, from initial analysis to uncovering its hidden operations. 2024-12-29</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/index.html</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Technologies Sentifender Lexica Detectica Sentifender Lexica Detectica is a Streamlit app that offers an overview of tables in Microsoft Sentinel and Defender, complete with pivot points between the tables and Kusto pivot examples. By using this tool you will get a better understanding on how you can move between the various tables.&#xA;Sentifender Lexica Detectica is available here Threat Hunting Threat Hunt by Predefender My notebook on Threat Hunting. This page serves as a compendium of my insights into Threat Hunting, presented in book format. After years of establishing SOC departments for several Norwegian cybersecurity firms while actively working as a threat hunter, I’ve chosen to share my notes and reflections on the craft of threat hunting. Now, as I transition into managing a Cyber Security Operations Center (CSOC), I believe it’s time to impart my perspective to empower SOC analysts to start as effective threat hunters from the outset.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/index.html</guid>
      <description>CTF Writeups SANS Holiday Hack Challenge 2024 The SANS Holiday Hack Challenge is an annual cybersecurity event featuring interactive challenges and a captivating storyline. Participants solve puzzles, tackle cybersecurity scenarios, and explore digital forensics, penetration testing, and other topics. It is designed for all skill levels, from beginners to seasoned professionals. The event is free and encourages collaboration, creativity, and learning. It culminates in a festive, gamified environment that combines technical training with holiday cheer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/index.html</guid>
      <description>Roger Johnsen Roger Johnsen is a dedicated Information Security Consultant specializing in enhancing Blue Team capabilities. His expertise includes educating analysts, developing threat hunting strategies, software development, and ensuring the quality assurance of processes and routines.&#xA;Roger actively participates in Capture The Flag (CTF) competitions on platforms like the SANS Holiday Hack Challenge and Hack The Box, integrating the knowledge gained into his daily practice. In 2022, he was recognized as the runner-up for the best “Technical Answer” in the SANS Holiday Hack Challenge 2021 edition, earning a challenge coin for his outstanding performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/index.html</guid>
      <description>I’m usually available for a chat. Just scan the QR code below if you are using Whatsapp. Quick note: I won’t accept voice or video calls without prior notification. Please keep in mind, don’t just say hi - state your question at the very start! Other Media Username / link LinkedIn Public profile Telegram @rjohnsen X / Twitter @rogercbjohnsen Mastodon @rjohnsen</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>